Guide to the Ladyslipper, Inc. Records, 1965-2011 and undated RL.10140
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Marketing and Promotional Series, 1976-2006; 2
  - Catalogs, 1976-2006; 2.1
    - Ladyslipper Catalog Supplement, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Wholesale Catalogs, Graphics, and Ads subseries, 1977-1999; 2.2
    - Wholesale catalogs, 1996-1998, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Wholesale Catalogs--Old, 1977-1990; 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Catalog Materials, 1980, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Catalog Materials, 1983, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - 1985 Cat Cover Artwork, 1984-1987; 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Therese's article for 1987 catalog, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 55)
    - 91-92 Cover, 1986-1994; 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Grafix Fall 95, 1995; 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Wholesale Blurb, 1994; 1 folders (Box 55)
    - 1992 Holiday Cover, 1980; 1 folders (Box 55)
    - CD-ROM- Catalog on?, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Cassette Flap for Catalogs, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Grafix Spring & Fall, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Catalogs Trivia Contest (nonwinners), 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Catalog Text, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Possible Grafix, 1996, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Cover Art- Catalog 1995 & 1996, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Spring Catalog Count--Analysis etc. 1996, 1993-1995; 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Back Covers Reserved 1997, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Cover art, catalog, 1997-1999, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Logos, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Graphics (2 folders) (Box 55)
    - Press type lines-graphics, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Cover type, cover boxes, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Category heads, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Heads in Lithograph LT, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - LS Logos, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Typefaces, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Graphix, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Graphics Listening Parties, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - New Age Grafix, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Rock Grafix, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - World Grafix, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Classical Graphics, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Country Grafix, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Holiday Grafix, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Men Grfx, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Misc. Grfx, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Video Grafix, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Spoken Grfx, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Women's Grfx, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Cards/Calendars, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Soundbook & Misc. Grafix, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Listen Line Grafix & Stuff, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Alt. Rock Grfx, 1 folders (Box 55)
    - Blues Grfx, 1 folders (Box 55)
  - Catalog Related Material subseries, 1979-2002; 2.3
    - Printing Quotes, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Gannett, 1995-2003; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Atlanta P.O. Permit, 1979-1998; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Catalog on Quark, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Triangle Web, 1995; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - NCOA, 1999; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Retail Mailing Early 2000, 1998-2000; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Spring 2001 Mailings--Retail, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Fall 2000 Mailings Retail, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Spring 00--Mailing, 2000; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Mail Plans--Holiday 2001, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Summer --Fall 2001 Wholesale Catalog, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Fall 2001 Mailing, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - MS Mailing List-American List Council, 1984-1994; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Fall 99 Mailing, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Amerisound International, 1994-1999; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Mailing Sprimg 99?, 1998; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Lists Ordered, Spg '98, 1998; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Mail Plans, Fall 1998, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Fall Mailing--1997, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Lists Ordered-Spg 97, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Catalog Printing, 1981-1985; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Non-Profit Bulk Mail Rates, 1985; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Advertising, 1981-1986; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Ladyslipper Ads-Biz card size, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Ads- Fall '96, 1996; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Ads-Spg '96- Non-Wholesale, 1996; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Fall '95 WH Ads- confirmed, 1995; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Wholesale Ads-Spring '95, 1994-1995; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Wholesale Ads-Fall '94, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Ads--1994, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - 1994-wh ad-- send info, 1993; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Want WH Ad Info Fall 1994, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Wholesale Ad Sheets, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - 1994 Catalog; WH Ads Confirmed, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Ads Confirmed--1994 Retail Cat, 1993; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Ladyslipper Ads, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Spring 93 Ads Confirmed, 1993; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Needs Ad Rates for Spring 1993, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - 1993-send wh ad rates, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - 1993 retail cat-ad reservations, 1992; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - 1993 catalog ads--send rate sheets, 1992; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Spring 92 and reservations-yes!, 1992; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Spring '92-send ad info, 1991; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Confirmed ads 1991, 1990; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Potential adverisers--1991 sent rate sheets, 1990; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Confirmed ads fall 1991 (1992 cat), 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Confirmed ads, 1989, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - 1989 advertisers--send rate card, 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - New ad requests ideas, 1986-1988; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - 1988 Catalog Ads, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - 1987 catalog ads, 1985-1987; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Send advertising, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Send ad info--fall '91, 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Confirmed ads-spg. 1991, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - WH Update Advertising, 1992; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - WH Ads 1991 fall-confirmed, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Wholesale Ad rates, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Wholesale ad rates--others, 1991; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Wholesale ads--Summer '97, 1997; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Mins-Spring 97, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Staff recommendations, 1996; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Spring 96 Ad $, 1996; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Ads Retail--1996 fall & web, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Grafix Spring 1995, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Boxes--Down, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Boxes, 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Boxes--Up, 1 folders (Box 56)
  - Advertisements subseries, 1992-2002; 2.4
    - Ads Placed 1994, 1994-2000; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Holiday Catalog Advertising Winter 1992-1993, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - 1993 Wholesale Ads Confirmed, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Wholesale Ads, 1994; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Send Ad Info 1994 catalog, 1993; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Wholesale Ad Center 1995 Spring, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Ad Rates, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Loop Program, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Ad Projects Spring 1999, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Spring 99 Ad Possibilities, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Advertising Spring 99, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Back Cover--Winter 98-99, 1998; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Ads Retail Winter 98, 1998; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Holiday 2001 Retail Res., 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Fall Retail Ads 2001, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Spring 2001 Wholesale Ad, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Spring 00 Retail Ads, 2000; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Catalog Ad Flyers, 1997-2002; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Planet Out, 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Ladyslipper Ads, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Ladyslipper Job Ads, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Holiday WH Supplement 2001 Ads, 2002-2004; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Lady Ads, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Spring 00 Retail Ads (Processed), 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Retail Winter 99-00, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Wholesale Ads Sprin 2002, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Spring Retail 2001 Ads, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Fall '00 Retail Ads, 2000; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Holiday 00 Retails Ads, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Wholesale Ads--Summer-Fall 00, 2000; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Spring 00 Retail Cover, 2000; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Spring 99-retail ads, 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Fall 99 Retail ads, 1999; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Winter 99-00 Wholesale supplement, 1999; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Back cover--Holcat 99-00, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Fall '98 Retail Ads, 1998; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Spring '99 Retail Ads, 1998; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Retail Edits for Spring '98 (deletions), 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Retail Text Changes, 1998; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Pages to Reprint Winter Catalog 98-99, 1998; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Spring 99 Back Covers, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Spring 99 Wholesale Ads, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Winter '98 Wholesale, 1998; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Wholesale Ads summer/fall 98, 1997-1999; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Balk Covers Fall '98, 1998; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Vendor co-op ads--not paid / for a/p approval, 1998; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Back covers--spring 1998, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Fall 98 WH ads not received, 1996-1998; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Fall 98 retail ads, 1998; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - 98 Holiday Wholesale Ads, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Retail catalog and rates, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Back covers--fall 97, 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Ad sheets, 1997; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Wholesale Ads Winter--Holiday 97, 1997; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Fall '97 Advertising, 1997; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Summer wholesale ads fall 97, 1997; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Spring 97 ads reserved, 1997; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Winter 97-98 ads retail, 1997; 1 folders (Box 57)
  - Festivals and Concerts subseries, 1977-2002; 2.5
    - American Booksellers Assocation, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - American Massage Therapy Association Convention 88, 1988; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Atlanta Pride '98, 1998; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Atlanta Pride, 1996; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Blues Skies Festival, 1997; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Camp Pleiades Labor Day '98, 1998; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Campfest '99, 1999; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Jessie Turner, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Camp Pleiades '97, 1997; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Camp Pleiades '96 Labor Day, 1996; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Camp Pleiades, 1998; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Campfest 1999, 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Campfest 1998, 1995-1999; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - DC Pride, 1997; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Campfest 1997, 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Campfest 96, 1996; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Campfest '95, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Campfest '94, 1994; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Campfest '93, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Campfest '92/womongathering, 1992; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Campfest '91, 1991; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Campfest '90, 1990; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Lisa-Campfest, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Campfest 88, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Campfest 89 womonogathering 89, 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Camp Out 2002, 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Duke Springfest 98, 1998; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - East Coast Lesbian Festival '93, 1993; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - East Coast Lesbian Festival '91, 1991; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Eno Fest '99, 1999; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Eno Fest, 1998; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Eno Festival '98, 1998; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - March on Washington '93, 1993; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - East Coast Lesbian Festival '92, 1992; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - East Coast Lesbian Festival '94, 1994; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Feminist Expo, 1996; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - In Gaia's Lap '97, 1997; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - In Gaia's Lap '96, 1996; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Maryland Womens Gathering--In Gaia's Lap '94, 1994; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Michigan Festival '01, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - MI Fest 2001, 1 folders (Box 58)
    - MI Fest 2000, 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Michigan '99, 1997-1999; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Michigan '98, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Michigan Fest '97, 1996-1997; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Michigan '96, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Michigan '95, 1995; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Michigan '94, 1994; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - MI Fest '93, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Michigan '92, 1991-1992; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Michigan Fest '91, 1991; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - WWTMC '90, 1990; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Michigan '89, 1989; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - 88 WWTMC, 1988-1990; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - National Black Lesbian Conference '01, 2001; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - National Women's Music Festival 1997, 1 folders (Box 58)
    - National Women's Music Festival '95, 1995; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - National Women's Music Festival '94, 1994; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - National Women's Music Festival '93, 1 folders (Box 58)
    - National Women's Music Festival '92, 1992; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - National Women's Music Festival '91, 1991; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - National Women's Music Festival '90, 1989; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - National Women's Music Festival '89, 1989; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - National Women's Studies Association '99, 1999; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - National Women's Studies Association '93 (2 folders), 1993 (Box 58)
    - National Women's Studies Conference '89, 1 folders (Box 58)
    - National NOW Confernce '87 Philly, 1987-1988; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - North East Women's Musical Retreat 1990, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - North East Women's Musical retreat '88, 1988; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - National Lesbian Conference '91, 1991; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Northampton Festival '94, 1994; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - NYC Pride, 1996; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Richmond Pride '96, 1996; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Richmond Women's Music Festival '95, 1995; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Daily Sales Sheets Rhythmfest, 1990; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Southeastern Conference for Lesbians and Gay Men '90, 1990; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Sisters Act '96, 1996; 1 folders (Box 58)
    - Lesbian Festival July 1991 Sydney, 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterfire '89, 1989; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Rhythmfest '94, 1988-1994; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Rhythmfest '95, 1995; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Rhythmfest, 1990; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Rhythmfest '92, 1992; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Rhythmfest '93, 1993; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Rhythmfest '91, 1991; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Rhythmfest '90, 1990; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Richmond Pride '96, 1996; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - S.C. Pride '98, 1998; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterfire '88, 1988; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterplace '01, 2001; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterspace '01, 2001; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterspace 2000, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterspace '95, 1995; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterspace '96 (2 folders), 1996 (Box 59)
    - Sisterfire '87, 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterspace '94, 1994; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterspace '93, 1993; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterspace Weekend 1996, 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterspace '92, 1992; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterspace '88, 1988; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Southern Womyn's Festival 2000, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterspace '88, 1988; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Southern Festival 2002, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Southern Festival '01, 2001; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - SWMCF '92, 1992; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - SWMCF '91, 1990-1991; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sales Sheets, 1990; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - SWMCF '90, 1989-1990; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - SWMCF '89, 1988-1991; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - SWMCF '88, 1987-1990; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Virginia Women's Festival-Intouch '96, 1996; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Tent, 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Virginia Women's Music Festival '93, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Virginia Women's Festival '97, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Virginia Women's Festival/Intouch '94, 1994; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Virginia Women's Festival 1999, 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Campout, VA Music Festival '01 May 25-27, 2001; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Viriginia Women's Festival '99, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Virginia Women's Festival '98, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Womongathering '99, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Womongathering '97, 1997; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Womongathering '98, 1998; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Womongathering, 1998; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Cris and Tret Concerts, 1995; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Miscellaneous Concert Sheets, 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Directions to Shows, 2000; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Festival Hints, 1992; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Gala Fest 2000, 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sweet Honey Concert Forms, 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Directions to Sweet Honey shows, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterspace '02 Sept. 13-15, 2002; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - DC Pride '98, 1998; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Atlanta Pride, 1998-; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - LS Concert Report Forms, 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - New England Women's Musical Retreat, 1980-1981; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - NCGLC March 83, 1982-1983; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sisterfire, 1982-1984; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Yosemite (West Coast Women's Music Festival), 1981; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Women's Jazz Festival, 1978-1982; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - NAMF '86, 1986-1987; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - National Women's Music Festival, 1977-1985; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Michigan Womyn's Music Festival, 1979-1984; 1 folders (Box 59)
    - Sweet Honey in the Rock-Baltimore Matt & Brauer, 1998; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Cris and Tret Asheville, 1998; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Cris and Tret Charlotte, 1998; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Ship Birchmere, 1998; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Mischellaneous Concert Sales, 1996-2002; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Sweet Honey in the Rock-Blue Bell, 1998; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Sweet Honey in the Rock-Asheville, 1998; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Sweet Honey Shows, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Ladyslipper Holiday Sale 1998, 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Cris and Tret Annapolis, 1998; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Sweet Honey Sales, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - MI Fest 2002, 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Festival shit, 1993-1999; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - In Gaia's Lap '94, 1994; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Notes for Lady Fest 1996, 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Mini Fest Info, 1994; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Rhythm Fest '94, 1994; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Cris Williamson, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Atlanta Pride '97, 1997; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Baltimore Pride '97, 1997-1999; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Baltimore Pride, 1997; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Blues Skies Festival, PA, 1997; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Miscellaneous Sales, 1997; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - DC Pride, 1997; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - DC Pride-June 8, 1997; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Eno Fest '02, 2002; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Eno Fest '01 June 30 July1 &4, 2001; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Feminist Expo 2000, 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Gala Choruses, 1996; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - The Gathering, 1995; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - GLAMA '95, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Phila Molly/Iris 5/20/01, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Margie Adam, 1992-1994; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Lucie Blue Tremblay, 1994; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Susan Herrick, 1994; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Holiday Sale Pall Sheets, 1997; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - In Touch, 1997; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Isis Crisis-Debbo & Sam, 1994; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Kay Gardner, 1998; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Ladyslipper 20th Anniversary Celebration '96, 1996; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Ladyslipper Holiday Sale, 1991-1997; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Michigan Womyn's Festival '95, 1995; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Philadelphia Pride 6-8, 1997; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Rockrgrl 11/00, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Sisterspace '95, 1995; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Sweet Honey in the Rock '96, 1991-2002; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Sweet Honey in the Rock-Miami, 1997; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Teresa Trull & Barb Higbee, 2001; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Womangathering 1997, 1996; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Campfest '96, '95, 1995-1996-; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Feminist Expo '96, 1996; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Romanovsky & Phillips '96, 1996; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Rhythmfest, 1995; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - OUT Charlotte- '96, 1996; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Holly Near, 1992-2000; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Cris/Tret, 1995-2000; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Pride NC, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - NC Pride, 1997; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - NC Pride '96, 1996; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - NWMF, 1995; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - East Coast Lesbian Festival, 1992; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - NOW's 25th anniversary, 1992; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Bobby McFerin & Voice extra, 1992; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Creating Change Conf., 1993; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - National Women's Studies Conference, 1993; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - March on Washington, 1993; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Sweet Honey on the Rock, 1995; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Teresa Trull Barbara Higbie, 1992; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Tiye, 1992; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Libana, 1992; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Jamie Anderson, 1993; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Alix Dobkin, 1993; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Kate Clinton, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Ubaka, 1997; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Womongathering '96, 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Frau und Musik, 1980; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - National Women's Music Festival 1991, 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Kay Concert-Grant Form, 1984; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Concert Report Forms, 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Concert Training, 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Campfest '87, 1987; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Campfest '85, 1985; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Campfest '84, 1984; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Music Industry Conference 1985, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - NAIRD '85, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - NWMF '86 / MIC '86, 1986; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - NWMF '85 (2 folders), 1985 (Box 61)
    - NWMEC '84, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - NWMF '83, 1983; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - NWSA '87 Atlanta Spelman Conference, 1984-1990; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - NWSA, 1984; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - National NOW Conference '83, 1983; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Sisterfire '85, 1985; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Sisterfire '84, 1981-1987; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - SWMCF '87, 1987; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - SWMCF '86, 1986; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - SWMCF '85, 1 folders (Box 61)
    - SWMCF 1984, 1 folders (Box 61)
    - WWTMC '87, 1987; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - WWTMC '86, 1985-1988; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - WWTMC 1985, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - WWTMC-Michigan '84, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Michigan 1983, 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Michigan '82 Sales Etc., 1982; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Michigan Sales '87, 1981; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Michigan Festival Sales '80, 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Winter Womyn Festival '87, 1987; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Winter Womyn Music I 1987, 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Listening Parties Liz--Flyers Expenses Etc., 1984; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Every Woman Festival, Norfolk, 1984; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - ODU Every Woman's Festival 1983, 1982-1984; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Roanoke--First Friday, 1981-1982; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - First Friday Retreat '84, 1984; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - SE Woman Employment Coalition, 1984; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - SECLGM '85, 1984-1985; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Newport News Fall Festival, 1985; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - International Women's Music Fest, 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - FL Now Convention '85, 1985; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - NWPC--1985, 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Southern Lesbian Conference 1984, 1 folders (Box 61)
    - NEWMR, 1983; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Festival Evaluation Forms CMAS, 1983; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Debbie Fier Concert '83, 1983; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Ferron Concert '82 Tour, 1982; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Ferron Concert '83, 1983; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Alix Concer '83, 1983; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - Album Covers, 1992-1994; 1 folders (Box 61)
    - PMT's of Album Covers-Minis, 1983; 1 folders (Box 61)